SAI MOUNICA GUDIMELLA

Website: https://saimounicagudimella.github.io/MyWebsite/
Tel: +91-9620006348 | Email: mounica500110@gmail.com

SUMMARY

A professional with a rich consulting experience working currently at Deloitte as a Business Analyst. Having a penchant for data analytics, I have completed Data Scientist with Python track on DataCamp.

I have learnt and applied Exploratory Data Analysis concepts on few datasets. Aware of Data Cleaning, manipulation and visualization techniques along with supervised and unsupervised machine learning analysis models.

Also working on a personal website in my pastime to build my portfolio.

EDUCATION

CMR INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, Bangalore	August 2013 – July 2017
Bachelor of Engineering (B.E), Computer Science and Engineering	76.02%
NARAYANA PU COLLEGE, Bangalore	March 2016 – April 2017
Karnataka State Board (Twelfth Class)	81%
INDIAN SCHOOL MUSCAT, Muscat	March 2014 – April 2015
CBSE (Tenth Class)	9.6/10 CGPA

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

DELOITTE CONSULTING INDIA PVT. LTD

HYDERABAD, INDIA

Analyst, Human Capital Management- Workday Integrations

April 2018 – Present

- Certified Workday Core HCM Consultant with 2.5 years' Workday experience
- Completed three project lifecycles by implementing Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) Workday application to transform Telstra's (Telecom giant in Australia) ERP system as one cloud ERP human capital management system
- Collaborated closely with client stakeholders across different geographical locations to gather requirements in order to design, build and test integration systems. Worked independently & effectively with cross-functional design teams to create software solutions that elevated clientside experience and significantly improved overall functionality and performance
- Visited the client site in Melbourne for leading and monitoring the E2E testing process within a year of joining Deloitte
- Developed integrations using the interfaces Studio, EIB, API, Connectors, Custom reports, Webservices. Adept at transforming data using XML, XSLT, SOAP, REST. Currently an SME for Learning and payroll module Integrations
- Worked on complex global payroll integrations by implementing ADP Streamline and Globalview using PECI and PICOF for 7 countries(India, Philippines, Hong Kong, Singapore, Malaysia, USA and

- UK). Implemented Supplemental integrations to support Time off, Leave of absences impacting payroll
- Trained on Prism Analytics, Core HCM, Recruitment & Absence functional module configurations
 & business processes

TIBCO SOFTWARE INC.

HYDERABAD, INDIA

Junior Consultant, Master Data Management

July 2017 - April 2018

- Trained in Master Data Management and TIBCO Integration stack
- Managed over 20+ tables in an RDBMS setup in the Dev, QA & Prod environments. This involved creation of tables, joining , performing complex queries using PL/SQL. Worked for the client JetBlue
- Worked on major enhancements to the tools to optimize them for performance and scalability challenges. Also gathered requirements to incorporate those changes in the design systems

SOFTWARE AG

BANGALORE, INDIA

Intern, R&D

January 2017 - April 2017

- Developed a feature in automated testing tool which helps in converting ill-structured, deformed commands into accurate testing statements using Stanford CoreNLP library
- This enables user to provide a command in plain English and the product would interpret the command to the closest possible test statement
- This is done by employing autocorrect mechanism for incorrect spellings and semantic analysis to find closest match for a word using Levenshtein Edit Distance Algorithm

NON-ACADEMIC PROJECTS

Personal Website – A personalized website built using HTML5, CSS3 and Bootstrap4 and hosted on GitHub to give an insight on my personal and professional attributes. (**InProgress**)

Link - https://saimounicagudimella.github.io/MyWebsite/

Drum Kit – A fun and stressbuster musical producing drum kit, developed using the web development languages.

Link - https://saimounicagudimella.github.io/Drum-Kit/

Simon Game – Developed an interactive memory game which lights buttons in a random order, after which the player must reproduce that order by pressing the buttons. As the game progresses, the number of buttons to be pressed increases

Link - https://saimounicagudimella.github.io/Simon-Game/

Dice Challenge – A simple rolling dice webpage, which produces different dice number on refreshing the page. Built using JavaScript, HTML5 and CSS3

Link - https://saimounicagudimella.github.io/Dicee-Challenge/

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

CMR INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

Bangalore, India

Question Paper Generator – Generates a question paper on the fly based on various parameters - difficulty level, number of questions, total marks. These options are available on UI developed using HTML5, CSS3 and Bootstrap. The questions are stored in the backend in a database

Aqualife-2D – Developed an interactive game which performs various tasks on selection using OpenGL, computer graphics

SKILLS

<u>Courses:</u> Database Management Systems, C++, Java, Operating Systems, Data Structures with C, Design and analysis of Algorithms, UNIX and shell programming, Software Engineering, Complier Design, Web Programming Languages, Tableau

Languages: Python, C, C++, Java, SQL, PL/SQL, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap4

<u>Certifications:</u> Data Scientist with Python - (Data Camp), MS Office(Microsoft Excel Certified) - (Udemy), Learning Data Analytics - (LinkedIn), SQL (Udemy)

<u>Libraries</u>: NumPy, Pandas, Scikit-Learn, Matplotlib, Seaborn

Exams: GRE – 311, TOEFL - 111

LEADERSHIP AND VOLUNTEERING

DELOITTE CONSULTING INDIA PVT. LTD

April 2018 – Present

- Impact Day 2018 Core Committee member and led the thread for "Isha Vidhya Foundation" with various activities consisting of members close to 600. This activity comprised of creating handmade books with insightful information, which in turn was sent to students from lower economic background
- **Resume Evaluation** Screen resumes obtained for Workday service line to find best match to further the interview process
- **Buddy Program** Help newly onboarded employees at Deloitte get accustomed to the workplace, ethics, culture, colleagues at Deloitte
- Impact Day 2019 Core Committee member and led the thread for "Wings to Fly Youth for Seva". The day involved teaching and conducting various activities to underprivileged students and empowering them with the need for literacy
- Offsite Core member responsible for the communications thread within the service line and for conducting various engagement activities to the practitioners
- Impact Day 2020 Core Committee member and led the thread for "Pratham Telangana". The
 day involved teaching and conducting various knowledge sessions for primary school students
 remotely

CMR INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

August 2013 - July 2017

- **Student Assistant** Helped professor conduct junior classes/seminars, prepare exam papers and grade answer sheets and assignments for Database Management Systems and Software Engineering courses.
- Class Representative Elected by peers to represent them for four consecutive semesters by coordinating between students and administration
- Microsoft Student Partner Responsible for learning new technologies and innovations from sessions conducted at Microsoft and to impart them at college
- Cultura Conducted and participated in various events at the Annual college fest